800!
NEEEEY!
Jump down from there!
For example, we can look at the perhaps clearest Swedish Christmas films.
That is, they have either Christmas or the plot in the title.
Just like our favorite poem.
Let me resite the first 7-8 verses.
Midwinter's cold is hard.
The stars, sparkle and glimpse.
Everyone sleeps in solitary yard, deep during midnight.
The moon wanders its silent track, the snow shines white on pine and spruce.
The snow shines white on the roofs.
Only the plot is awake.
Have I really taken it is right?
This woman
Sara, who we will celebrate Christmas with, has three children with three different men.
You sometimes.
She lives along with one
Fourth, some Janne who has no children of their own.
And everyone will be there.
But new wives.
The plot is the father of all the children is about
A couple where the man has sterilized himself sneakily.
It's called sterilized.
But it is
quietly go on with yours.
I will not disturb.
She has fertilized herself sneakily and now this will get some resolution on Christmas Eve.
It is not directly cozy on the couch with the family.
I've been worse.
Plus, if you are in a couple relationship you might be able to talk to each other.
Instead of trying to solve everything on December 24 as two fucking ...
Yes, two fucking ...
Doesn't he see the text that is being prosecuted?
It must be how much fucking Christmas it wants.
But this will be the report on.
If you don't have much, very good explanation now.
I saw the plot.
Kiss, mom, me ...
Okay, but you, there is a movie series that has succeeded.
No matter how stolen Sigge Eklund claims it is.
Right?
Yes, unfortunately, a small problem has arisen due to overbooking.
I wonder about Olsson Stig-Helmer.
Actually, I think the Sällskapsresan is
The only real Christmas movie on this list.
Christmas gift distribution.
And by that I mean that it actually to
Most of them take place during Christmas leave.
And those who are on the trip seem to care a little about it being Christmas.
Talk about unreal.
Although the pig party and Peppes Bodega are of course more important.
Sexier you get to look for.
Sure, it's a bit creepy that Stig-Helmer
Love interests are always as old throughout the film series.